Guide to the Lewis Zurlo Associates Architecture & Interior Design Collection MS 028
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Project Photographs, 46737
  - Bishop Curtis Homes, undated; 46929 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 7-11)
    2 8½ x 11 color photocopies
  - Bishop Curtis Homes, undated; 46928 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 1)
    1 4x5 color negative
  - Bishop Curtis Homes (93-01), undated; 46927 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    52 4x6 color and negatives
    26 4x6 color
    4 3½ x 5 color
  - Brushy Hill Renovation (87-17), undated; 46926 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    22 3½ x 5 color and negatives
  - Butts Porch (73-04), undated; 46925 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 12)
    3 5x7 color
  - Buzaid Residence Negatives (Model), undated; 46924 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 1)
  - Churches (negatives), undated; 46923 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 1)
    New Hope Baptist, United Methodist New Milford, and First Congregational Chapel, New Milford
  - CityCenter Building/Omaha Beef (93-09), undated; 46922 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    11 4x6 color and negatives
  - Coffee Please, 258-262 Main St. (99-52), undated; 46921 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    10 4x6 color
  - Community Health Center (97-19), undated; 46920 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    21 4x6 color
  - Comstock Interior (92-11), undated; 46919 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    10 3½ x 5 color
  - Curren Residence (92-15), undated; 46918 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    18 4x6 color and negatives
  - Danbury Medical Group (95-14), undated; 46917 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    Color negatives
  - Danbury Senior Center (20-03), undated; 46916 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    54 4x6 color and negatives
  - 100 Danbury Road (94-04), undated; 46915 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    5 4x6 color and negatives
  - DeLucia Apartments (89-06), undated; 46914 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 13)
    9 4x6 color
  - DeLucia Apartments (89-06), undated; 46913 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    8 4x6 color and negatives
  - DeVoe Insurance Building Façade (84-05), undated; 46912 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 14)
    2 5x7 color
    6 8x10 color
    2 8x12 color
    1 5x8 color
    2 8x10 b/w
  - DeVoe Insurance Building Façade (84-05), undated; 46911 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 2)
  - DeVoe Insurance Building Façade (84-05), undated; 46910 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    6 3½ x 5 color and negatives
    1 4x6 color
  - DeVoe New Milford Site Plans Study (86-27), undated; 46909 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 15)
    2 8½ x 11 color
  - DeVoe New Milford Site Plans Study (86-27), undated; 46908 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 2)
  - Downtown Buildings & Danbury Buildings, undated; 46907 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    19 4x6 color
    North Main Street: 4 4x6 color
    Danbury: One 3½ x 5 and 5 4x6 color
  - Downtown Danbury Improvement Plan, undated; 46906 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 16-18)
    1 8x10 color
    3 7x10½ color photocopies
    7 8½ x 11 color photocopies
    Clippings, conceptual designs, qualifications
  - Downtown Danbury Improvement Plan, undated; 46905 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 2)
    7 4x5 color negatives
  - Downtown Danbury Façade Program (14x15 Multi-Ring Binder), undated; 46904 (Box OS 6, Folder *)
    8 8x14 b/w
    11 8x10 b/w
    7 7x9 b/w
    2 5x12 b/w
    9 b/w drawings (copies) of street facades 10x14
    6 contact sheets w/negatives
  - Downtown Danbury Façade Program: Blueprint #1: East side of Main Street (@ ¼" scale, undated; 46903 (Box OS 6, Folder *)
    elevation in continuous roll
    (15"x163")
  - Downtown Danbury Façade Program: Blueprint #2: Same as above @ 1/20" scale, undated; 46902 (Box OS 6, Folder *)
    (6"x68")
  - Downtown Danbury Façade Program: Blueprint #3: Same as above @ 1/32" scale (3 1/3"x 42"), undated; 46901 (Box OS 6, Folder *)
  - Downtown Danbury Façade Program: Blueprint #4: Partial elevation of White Street @, undated; 46900 (Box OS 6, Folder *)
    1/20th scale ((7"x2'=2")
  - Downtown Danbury Redevelopment, undated; 46899 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 19-20)
    19-20
    7 8x10 color
    One 4x6 color
    5 8½ x 11 color photocopies
    Clippings
  - Downtown Danbury Redevelopment, undated; 46898 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    3 4x6 color and negatives
  - Duncan Apartments, 20-51, undated; 46897 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - Dunkin Donuts, Mill Plain & Lake Avenue (92-18), 1992; 46896 (Box ?, Folder *)
    7 4x6 color and negatives
  - Dunkin Donuts, Bethel (91-09), undated; 46895 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    6 4x6 color
    3 3½ x 4 color Polaroid
  - 100 Elm Street and Barn (91-07), undated; 46894 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 21-23:)
    124 4x6 color prints/negatives
    9 3½ x 4 Polaroid (color)
    4 8½ x11 color photocopies
  - 100 Elm Street and Barn (91-07), undated; 46893 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 3)
    Negatives
  - Ericson House Reconstruction (not built), 1989-2000; 46892 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 24)
    39 4x6 color
    3 3½ x 4 Polaroid color
    One 2x2 b/w mounted on black board
  - Ericson House Reconstruction (not built),Negatives, 1989-2000; 46891 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 4)
  - Ermert Residence (92-02), undated; 46890 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - First Congregational Chapel, New Milford (68-02), undated; 46889 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 25)
    2 4x4 color
    2 4x6 color
    4 5x5 color
    9 3x3 color
    One 8 ½ x 11 color photocopy
    Letter
  - Galleria Interior (93-19), undated; 46888 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    1st floor south, 14 4x6 color
    1st floor north, 17 4x6 color
    3rd floor, 15 4x6 color
  - Galleria Interior (93-19), undated; 46887 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    Opening, 31 4x6 color
    2nd floor, 9 4x6 color
  - Galleria Union Savings (91-03), undated; 46886 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 1-4)
    1 5x7 color
    10 8x10 color
    5 8x10 color photocopies
    2 8x10 color photocopies (mounted)
    Cost estimate, clippings.
  - Galleria Union Savings (91-03), undated; 46885 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 5)
    10 4x5 color negatives
  - Galleria Union Savings (91-03), undated; 46884 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    69 4x6 color
    63 4x6 color
    General negatives
  - Garofalo Addition (84-13), undated; 46883 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - Godfrey Apartments, undated; 46882 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 5)
    2 8x10 color photocopies
  - Godfrey Apartments, undated; 46881 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 5)
    2 4x5 color negatives
  - Halpin Court, Ridgefield (85-09), undated; 46880 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 6)
    4 3½ x 4 color Polaroid
    3 3½ x 5 color (ex. of FMHA Elderly Housing)
  - Halpin Court, Ridgefield (85-09), undated; 46879 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 6)
  - Halpin Court, Ridgefield (85-09), undated; 46878 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    56 4x6 color and negatives
  - Harrison Square (99-49), undated; 46877 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    25 4x6 color
  - Hatter's Yard (87-05), undated; 46876 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 7-8)
    8 8x10 color
    18 4x6 color
    Clippings, housing submittal and project req.
  - Hatter's Yard (87-05), undated; 46875 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 6)
    7 8½ x 11 color negatives (site plans)
  - Hatter's Yard (87-05), undated; 46874 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    32 4x6 color and negatives
  - Hearthstone Castle (93-18), undated; 46873 (Box Photo_box 6)
    (87 4x6 color), includes Conceptual Construction Cost Estimate by LPR dated 2/16/95. (2 c)
  - Hearthstone Castle (93-18), undated; 46872 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hopponen Residence (93-08), undated; 46871 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - Horton Residence Model (Eliot Noyes Office, ca.1970), undated; 46870 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 9)
    6 3x4 b/w
  - Hudson's Restaurant (83-25), undated; 46869 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 10)
    1 8½ x 11 color photocopy
  - Hudson's Restaurant, Haverstraw Marina Restaurant, NJ (83-25), undated; 46868 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - Hull Building (83-28), undated; 46867 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 11-13)
    7 4x6 color
    3 8x10 b/w
    One 5½ x 5½ b/w
    Renews and newspaper clippings
  - Hull Building (83-28), undated; 46866 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 8)
    12 4x5 color negatives
    2 4x5 b/w negatives
    2 2½ x 2½ color negatives
  - Hull Addition (83-28), undated; 46865 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    16 3½ 5 color and negatives
  - IBM Projects - One Hamden Center (90-24), undated; 46864 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 14-18)
    89 4x6 color
    4 8½ x 11 color photocopies
  - IBM Projects - One Hamden Center (90-24), undated; 46863 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 9)
  - IBM Projects - One Hamden Center (90-24), undated; 46862 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 9)
    4 strips color negatives (Finals 8/7/91)
  - IBM Projects - One Hamden Center (90-24), undated; 46861 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
    5 8½ x 14 Evacuation Routes, Floors 1-4
  - IBM Projects - Hamden and Washington, D.C. (see also:, undated; 46860 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 19)
    31 4x6 color
  - IBM Projects - Negatives, undated; 46859 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 9)
  - IBM Projects - Hartford (Survey photos), undated; 46858 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 20)
    16 3½ x 5 b/w
    4 4x6 color
    One 8½ x 11 color photocopy
  - IBM Projects - Hartford (Survey photos) b/w negatives, undated; 46857 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 10)
  - IBM Projects - IBM Chairs, Route 7 Office Building, undated; 46856 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 21)
    14 4x6 color
  - IBM Projects - IBM Chairs, Route 7 Office Building, undated; 46855 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 10)
  - IBM Projects - 201 Merritt 7, Norwalk (89-22), undated; 46854 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 22-23)
    15 3½ x 5 color
    One 8x12 color
  - IBM Projects - Rolm, Stamford (92-13), undated; 46853 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 24)
    22 4x6 color
  - IBM Projects - Rolm, Stamford (92-13), undated; 46852 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 10)
  - IBM Projects - Rolm, Stamford (92-13), undated; 46851 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    14 4x6 color and negatives
    5 3½ x 5 color
  - Immaculate Garage & Playground, undated; 46850 (Box Photo_box 2, Folder 25)
    5 4x6 color prints
  - The Ives House Restoration, 1784 (89-11), undated; 46849 (Box Photo_box 3, Folder 1-9)
    139 4x6 color prints
    7 3½ x 4 Polaroid (color)
    21 8½ x 11 color photocopies
    Opening celebration booklet and newsletters.
    Clippings and photocopies w/notations.
    Report on Ives House compiles by Linda Warren, Yankee Intern Program, summer 1985
  - The Ives House Restoration, 1784 (89-11), undated; 46848 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 11)
  - The Ives House Restoration, 1784 (89-11), undated; 46847 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - Kentucky Fried Chicken Interior, (91-15), undated; 46846 (Box Photo_box 3, Folder 10)
    (See also: 100 Elm Street negatives)
  - Kentucky Fried Chicken Interior, (91-15), undated; 46845 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    6 4x6 color and negatives
  - Kramer's Framing? 10/94, undated; 46844 (Box Photo_box 3, Folder 11)
    One 4x5 color negative (interior sketch by Heather Zurlo)
  - Ladd's Hamburger Stand (New Milford), undated; 46843 (Box Photo_box 3, Folder 12)
  - Landwehr Interiors (94-11), undated; 46842 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - Leili Fire Rebuild/Leeds Office Bldg. (87-10), undated; 46841 (Box Photo_box 3, Folder 13)
    One 8½ x 11 color photocopies
  - Leili Fire Rebuild/Leeds Office Bldg. (87-10), undated; 46840 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 12)
    b/w negatives
  - Leili Fire Rebuild/Leeds Office Bldg. (87-10), undated; 46839 (Box Photo_box 3, Folder 14)
    Leili Passageway (rendering)
    b/w site plan
  - Leili Fire Rebuild/Leeds Office Bldg. (87-10), undated; 46838 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 12)
    One 4x5 color negative
  - Leonard Renovation (New Canaan) 75-03, undated; 46837 (Box Photo_box 3, Folder 15)
  - Levy Addition (Lake Candlewood) 73-05, undated; 46836 (Box Photo_box 3, Folder 16)
  - East Liberty, 12/30/89, undated; 46835 (Box Photo_box 3, Folder 17)
    4 8x10 b/w
  - East Liberty, 12/30/89, undated; 46834 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 13)
    10 4x5 b/w negatives
  - Liberty Terrace (91-02), undated; 46833 (Box Photo_box 3, Folder 18-23)
    8 8x10 color (incl. site plan)
    One 8x10 color (mounted)
    2 8½ x 11 b/w photocopies (rendering)
    One 8x20 b/w rear elevation (rendering)
    Clippings, magazine articles (Global Link), opening
  - Liberty Terrace (91-02), undated; 46832 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 14)
    One 8x10 color negative
    6 4x5 color negatives
  - Liberty Terrace (91-02), undated; 46831 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - The Old Library & Cultural Center, 1879 (86-03, 89-20), undated; 46830 (Box Photo_box 3, Folder 24-27)
    6 3½ x 5 color
    11 4x6 color
    6 5x7 color
    5 8½ x11 color photocopies
    1 8½ x11 color photocopy (mounted)
    Clippings, correspondence, plans
  - The Old Library & Cultural Center, 1879 (86-03, 89-20), undated; 46829 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
    3 10x14 b/w
  - The Old Library & Cultural Center, 1879 (86-03, 89-20), undated; 46828 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
    10 photographs (before pictures) mounted on 20½ x 8 foam core illustrating panoramic view of interior.
  - The Old Library & Cultural Center, 1879 (86-03, 89-20), undated; 46827 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 15)
    One 3½ x 5 color negative (mounted)
  - 15 Library Place (96-14), undated; 46826 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - 221 Main Street (93-12), undated; 46825 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    12 4x6 color and negatives
  - 258-268 Main Street, Store Facades/Signs (93-17), undated; 46824 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - Main Street (exterior behind 270 Main Street), undated; 46823 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 1)
    1 4x6 color (rendering)
    2 frames color negatives
  - Mall Stores (New York Snack Exchange), undated; 46822 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 2)
    One 8x10 color
    2 3½ x 4 color Polaroid
  - Mall Stores (New York Snack Exchange), undated; 46821 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 16)
    Color negatives (RooRooRoo)
  - Mall Stores (New York Snack Exchange), undated; 46820 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - 41-45 Maple Avenue (92-06), undated; 46819 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    8 4x6 color
  - Miller Residence (95-08), undated; 46818 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - Murphy Residence, New Fairfield (75-05), undated; 46817 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 3)
    6 5x7 b/w
  - Murphy Residence, New Fairfield (75-05), undated; 46816 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 16)
    4 3x4 b/w negatives
  - Music Guild Restoration, 1895 (84-07), undated; 46815 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 4)
    1 8x11 color
  - Music Guild Restoration, 1895 (84-07), undated; 46814 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 17)
    3 4x5 color negatives
  - Music Guild Façade, undated; 46813 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    3 3½ x 5 color and negatives
    5 3½ x 5 b/w
  - New Bethel Church of God (92-14), undated; 46812 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    26 3½ x 5 b/w and negatives
  - New Bethel Church of God (92-14), undated; 46811 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    113 4x6 color
    8 3½ x 4 color Polaroid
  - New Hope Baptist Church (75-02), undated; 46810 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 5)
  - New Rochelle (93-22), undated; 46809 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - Newtown Dental Associates (92-12), undated; 46808 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    17 4x6 color photographs
  - Nolan Enterprises Office (other projects), undated; 46807 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 6)
  - Northside Animal Hospital (85-20), undated; 46806 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 7-8)
    13 4x6 color
    26 3½ x 5 color
    One 8x10 b/w
  - Northside Animal Hospital (85-20), undated; 46805 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 18)
    4 strips 120 mm negatives
    One 8x10 negative (blueprint)
  - Palace View (97-42), undated; 46804 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    48 4x6 color
    One 3½ x 5 color
  - Paulo's Auto Repair (02-04), and Southgate Railing/, undated; 46803 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    Deck (03-05)
    Paulo's: 7 4x6 color and negatives
    Southgate: 20 4x6 color and negatives
  - Pernick Renovations/Library (93-02), undated; 46802 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    27 4x6 color
  - Phineas Park Apartments, Bethel (82-41), undated; 46801 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 9)
    4 8x10 color
  - Phineas Park Apartments, Bethel (82-41), undated; 46800 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 19)
  - Phineas Park Apartments, Bethel (82-41), undated; 46799 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - Radial Bearing (01-05), undated; 46798 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 10)
    18 3½ x 5 color
  - Negatives, undated; 46797 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 19)
  - Ranger Residence, Bear Mountain, (83-01), undated; 46796 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 11-12)
    29 4x6 color
    Includes drawings
  - Ranger Residence, Bear Mountain, (83-01), undated; 46795 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 20)
  - Residential (All), undated; 46794 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 13)
    11 5x7 color
    2 color photocopies
  - Rider Addition (Lake Waubeeka) 76-03, undated; 46793 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 14)
  - Ridgebury Church School, undated; 46792 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 15)
  - Russo Building I, undated; 46791 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 16)
    2 8½ x 11 color photocopy
  - Russo Building I, undated; 46790 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 20)
    One 4x5 b/w negative
  - Sandpit Condos (86-32), undated; 46789 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 17)
    11 3½ x 4 color Polaroid
  - Sandpit Condos (86-32), undated; 46788 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 21)
    8 4x5 b/w negatives
  - Savings Bank of Danbury Addition, 1995-1996; 46787 (Box Photo_box 7, Folder 19)
    192 4x6 color prints
    6 8x10 color prints
    6 4x5 negatives (mounted)
  - Savings Bank of Danbury Addition, 1995-1996; 46786 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 22)
  - Savings Bank Addition (97-15), undated; 46785 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    68 4x6 color and negatives
    Color negatives (93-15)
  - SBD Bank Branch Interior, New Milford, undated; 46784 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    10 4x6 color and negatives
  - SBD Loan Center (98-11), undated; 46783 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 18)
    Clippings, opening
  - SBD Loan Center (98-11), undated; 46782 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    64 4x6 color
    See SBD Hayestown Drive-Up Window for Interiors
  - SBD Loan Production, 211 Main Street (93-15A), undated; 46781 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    20 4x6 color and negatives
  - SBD Hayestown Drive-Up Window (93-15B), undated; 46780 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    SBD Loan Center Interiors (98-63)
  - Sienkiewicz Renovation (89-03), undated; 46779 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 19)
    46 4x6 color
    5 3½ x 4 color Polaroid
  - Sienkiewicz Renovation (89-03), undated; 46778 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 23)
  - Sipperly Wells Building (82-33), undated; 46777 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 20)
  - Sipperly Wells Building (82-33), undated; 46776 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 23)
  - Southworth Gymnastics (95-09), undated; 46775 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - SouthgateRailing/Deck (03-05), undated; 46774 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    See Paulo's Auto Repair (02-04)
  - Sperry Rail Hi-Car Design (94-14), undated; 46773 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 21)
    2 8½ x 11 before and after color photocopies
    One 8½ x 11 rendering of interior
  - Sperry Rail Hi-Car Design (94-14), undated; 46772 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    15 4x6 color and negatives
  - Tarrywile Lavatories, existing conditions (97-11), undated; 46771 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - Technomic Publishing, undated; 46770 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 22)
  - Towey Addition (78-05), undated; 46769 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 23)
  - Trauber Residence (95-02), undated; 46768 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    2 4x6 color and negatives
  - Tuxedo Junction/Alligator Alley (93-07), undated; 46767 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
  - Union National Bank, undated; 46766 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 24)
  - United Methodist Church (New Milford) 76-06, undated; 46765 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 25)
    4 3x5 color
  - Union Savings Bank, undated; 46764 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 26)
    1 8½ x 11 rendering
  - Venture 8, Greenwich 72-02, undated; 46763 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 27)
  - VFW Building, 1842 Second Meeting House (87-19), undated; 46762 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 28)
    Information regarding restoration
  - VFW Building, 1842 Second Meeting House (87-19), undated; 46761 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    29 3½ x 5 color
  - The Vincent Apartments (82-43), undated; 46760 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 29)
    23 4x6 color
  - The Vincent Apartments (82-43), undated; 46759 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 24)
    4 4x5 color negatives
  - Viola Addition (Brookfield) 73-01, undated; 46758 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 30)
  - Viola Addition (Brookfield) 73-01, undated; 46757 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
    One 10x14 color
  - Volkswagon of American, undated; 46756 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 31)
  - West Street, New Milford (94-01), undated; 46755 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    21 4x6 color and negatives
  - Westport Tennis Club, undated; 46754 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 32)
  - Wilton-Ridge, Sullivan Farms reference (94-05), undated; 46753 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    22 4x6 color and negatives
  - Wooster School (81-02), undated; 46752 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    50 3½ x 5 b/w
  - Wooster School (81-02), undated; 46751 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 25)
  - Worden Addition (87-09), undated; 46750 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    34 4x6 color
  - Zotos Inn, Liberty Street (80-16), undated; 46749 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Small Jobs, undated; 46748 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 34)
    New Bethel Town Hall (3 4x6 color)
    Brushy Hill (5 3½ x 5 color)
    6 Terrace Place (4 3½ x 5 color)
    Includes clippings of small jobs
  - Unidentified, 2 11x14 b/w, and one, undated; 46747 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
    11x14 color
  - Miscellaneous - Brookfield, CT (13 4x6 color), undated; 46746 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous - New Haven (7 4x6 color), undated; 46745 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous - New York State Bank (5 4x6 color), undated; 46744 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous - Philadelphia, PA (5 4x6 color), undated; 46743 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous - Portland, ME (12 4x6 color & negatives), undated; 46742 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous - Washington/Baltimore (60 4x6 color & negatives), undated; 46741 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 37-38)
  - Miscellaneous - Waterbury Ceasar Pelli Museum School (11 3½ x5 color, 6 4x6 color), undated; 46740 (Box Photo_box 4, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous - Negatives, undated; 46739 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Buildings (filed with Mall Stores), undated; 46738 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    14 3½ x 5 color